{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Lepage",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Canadian_dramatists_and_playwrights_in_French",
    "human_readable": "Robert Lepage is a subject of Canadian dramatists and playwrights in French.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9168201088905334,
            "question": "Is Robert Lepage recognized for his contributions to Canadian theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903007507324219,
            "question": "How has Robert Lepage influenced Canadian theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8124308586120605,
            "question": "Name some notable works by Robert Lepage."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6975942254066467,
            "question": "What is Robert Lepage known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6479038596153259,
            "question": "What category of artist is Robert Lepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6059227585792542,
            "question": "To which country does Robert Lepage belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5303642749786377,
            "question": "In what language do Robert Lepage's plays primarily exist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5294263958930969,
            "question": "Has Robert Lepage worked in any other artistic mediums besides playwriting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49129506945610046,
            "question": "Are there any specific themes or styles that characterize Robert Lepage's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3455451428890228,
            "question": "What are some of the awards or recognitions received by Robert Lepage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Lepage is a subject of Canadian dramatists and playwrights in French.",
            "html": "dbpedia_579_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific themes or styles that characterize Robert Lepage's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_579_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Robert Lepage worked in any other artistic mediums besides playwriting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_579_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what language do Robert Lepage's plays primarily exist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_579_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_579_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Robert Lepage being a Canadian writer, director, designer, and actor who works in theatre, film, and other forms of art. This supports the statement that he is a subject of Canadian dramatists and playwrights in French."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}